LUZ MYRIAM ENRIQUEZ

Jirón Paraíso № 815, Casa 3 – Urb. Sol de la Molina, La Molina, Lima – Perú

Cellular: (511) 9865 – 44750 / Home: (511) 479 – 0707

Imenriquez.v@gmail.com

Executive with 16 years of experience in mechanical and electric maintenance of industrial plants for companies in different sectors. Experienced in planning and project development, in the installation and putting in service of turbines and industrial equipment as well as the implementation of maintenance control computer systems.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SNC LAVALIN 20011 -2012

Worldwide Engineering and Construction Leading Company with operations in the industrial sector and provision of maintenance service.

Construction Electrical Engineer

Supervision and engineering duties during the construction of the 520 MW Combined Cycle Thermal Power Plant owned by Fénix Power Perú S.A.

Supervision of electrical works during the construction of the Thermal Power Plant Peru of the 520 MW Combined Cycle owned by Fenix Power Perú S.A.

- Inspection of the various areas of operational processes in construction with different subcontractors.
- Ensure the quality of the project and lead improvements and engineering changes.
- Validate materials, equipment and designs as per project specifications and standards.
 Management and materials and services purchase for the project in accordance with project schedules.

SN POWER PERU (Until 2009 "EMPRESA DE GENERACIÓN ELÉCTRICA CAHUA S.A.") Generates and markets electric power with an installed capacity of 268.624 MW, through 8 hydraulic power stations nationwide.

Chief of Maintenance Planning

2008 - 2009

Maintenance planning for 8 power stations, 39 substations and transmission lines. Managed 4 people and a budget of US\$5.2 millions; reported to Maintenance Manager.

- A 4 MW increase in effective power at Cahua mini power station through:
 - Optimization of efficiency in 1% by installing covered turbines which decreased maintenance costs and annual downtime in 15 days.
 - Updating of velocity and tension regulators as well as the hydraulic system, thus decreasing unplanned service outages and increasing output.
- Decreased operating costs at Pariac mini power station by updating its velocity control system with the implementation of remote operation control.

Chief of Planning and Maintenance

2006 - 2007

Integral maintenance management of 4 power stations for CAHUA S.A. as well as budget administration. Managed 25 people, reported to Operations Manager.

- Updated control system of Gallito Ciego power station, increasing its useful life in 15 years and raising the system's reliability.
- Decreased operational cost of Gallito Ciego power station by implementing a remote operation system, ran from Lima.
- Increased output in 10 MW, overhauling 4 mini power stations in Arcata and updating 3 at Pariac in a four-month timeframe.

- Implemented JobTech maintenance control computer system in Arcata and Pariac mini
 power stations, which provided better information for the maintenance plan and allowing its
 follow-up from Headquarters in Norway.
- Certified maintenance processes with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and ISO 18000, improving service quality, company image and working environment.

GENERAL ELECTRIC INTERNATIONAL INC.

Multinational company which provides installation, operation and maintenance services for gas turbines.

Field Engineer 2002 - 2006

Installation and maintenance of electric parts in turbines the in Latin-American region.

- Installed and put in service electric generating and excitation systems for 2 7FA gas turbines and two D11 steam turbines in Project Altamira V, Tampico, Mexico. Start-up accomplished in first try (zero failures).
- Updated excitation system and put in service MS500-TG09 gas turbine in CADAFE power station, La Fria, Venezuela, as project leader.
- Installed, commissioned and put in service two 7FA combined-cycle gas turbines, in two
 months less than forecasted, earning the client's recognition, in Project Termopernambuco
 of Iberdrola Group, Recife, Brazil.

ENERSUR S.A.

Power generating company of SUEZ Group, with 4 power stations in Peru and an installed capacity of 900 MW.

Chief of Section in Electricity, Instrumentation and Control Department 1997 - 2002 Electric equipment and control systems maintenance at 206 MW ILO1 thermal power station. Managed 13 people, reported to Maintenance Chief.

- Updated station's plant control system to INFI 90, increasing operational reliability and improving customer service and the company's image.
- Extended in 10 years the useful life of two of the station's turbines, participating in velocity regulators and excitation system update, which improved operational and maintenance control

SOUTHERN PERÚ COPPER CORPORATION - ILO Assistant Engineer

1996 - 1997

EMPRESA DE GENERACIÓN ELÉCTRICA DE AREQUIPA S.A.

Assistant Engineer

1996

Participated in the implementation and development of automation and commissioning of CHARCANI VI power station.

EDUCATION

Pontificia Universidad Católica del Perú

Specialization in Project and Quality Management, ongoing.

Universidad Nacional San Agustín de Arequipa, Perú

- Electronic Engineering, 1987 - 1994.

OTHER COURSEWORK

General Electric University, Schenectady – United States of America

Certification on "Excitation System and Retrofits - EX2100", 2004.

- Certification on "Electrical Direct Hire EE 02-6 (EX2000/LCI) and Generators", 2002.
- Certification on "Green Belt Six Sigma Quality", 2003.

Instituto del Sur, Arequipa, Perú

Specialization and Development Program: "Computer Systems Programming", 1995.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Peruvian, married with 1 son. Advanced user of computer systems, proficient in English.